FEBRIYADI

(+62) 853-9507-7795 | febriyadibangkit@gmail.com | github.com/pebbDev | linkedin.com/in/febriyadi-/ Palu, Central Sulawesi, Indonesia

SUMMARY

I am a 6th semester Informatics Engineering student who has a deep interest in Mobile Development and Web Programming. I have 1 year of experience in mobile application development, especially for Android platform using Kotlin and also 3 years of UI/UX skills. In addition, I deepened my knowledge and skills in cross-platform application development using Flutter. During my studies, I was often involved in web development projects both on a small and large scale. Evidence of my involvement can be seen from some of the projects I have worked on and also the achievements I have achieved. I am also active in several organizations to add relationships, experience, and soft skills. I am good at working in teams and leading projects and have successfully led the team to become the web app Winner of The Best Innovation And Impect category.

EDUCATION

Tadulako Univeristy

08/2021 - Present

Bachelor of Engineering - Major in Informatics Engineering;

3.85 of 4.00

Relevant Coursework: Basic Programming, Structure Data, Database, Software Engineering, Web Programming, Analysis and algorithm design, Mobile Programming, Cloud Computing, API, IMK, Kriptografi and Parallel.

EXPERIENCE

PT Bank Mandiri (Persero) Tbk

Full-Time

Project-Based Virtual Intern | Mobile Apps Developer

02/2024 - 03/2024

- Mentored directly by Bank Mandiri developers on Livin' by Mandiri app development, as well as Android and iOS app development skills.
- Build a news application using Jetpack Compose, MVVM, Clean Architecture, Data Store, and RoomDatabase.
- Using GitLab for collaboration and integration, and learning and implementing Restful API and unit testing. Leverage knowledge: Android, IOS, Gitlab.

Bangkit Academy by Google, GoTo, Traveloka

Remote, Jakarta

Cohort | Mobile Development Learning Path

08/2023 – 12/2023

- Learn soft skills such as Growth Mindset and Power of Feedback, Time Management, Critical Thinking and Problem Solving, Adaptability and Resilience, Project Management, Professional Communication and Networking, Professional Branding and Interview Communication and English.
- Develop our app for our team capstone project.
- Mastered advanced Android development topics: architecture, dependency injection, reactive programming, modularization, CI, security, performance, and testing (unit and instrumented).

Leverage knowledge: Kotlin, MVVM, API, Local Data Persistent, Clean Architecture, Testing, and SoftSkill.

IDCamp 2023 Remote, Jakarta Indosat Ooredoo Hutchison Digital Camp I Multi-platform App Developer

Mastery of Dart Fundamentals, OOP, and Functional Styles

08/2023 - 12/2023

- Learning Widgets in Flutter
- Consuming API News and State Management with setState and Provider Leverage knowledge: Dart, Flutter, OOP, Functional Styles, Widget, API, state management.

ORGANIZATION

Mentor | Media

Programming Tadulako

Palu. Indonesia 10/2023 - Present

- Create and lead teams to participate in various competitions, especially at the national level.
- Menjadi mentor dalam desain UI/UX menggunakan Figma.

Himpunanan Mahasiswa Teknologi Infromatika

Content Creation Leader | Creativity Department

Palu, Indonesia 04/2023 – Present

- Produce engaging visuals, including social media posts, videos and graphics.
- Produce creative ideas related to existing technologies and trends

Taman Baca TodeaPalu,IndonesiaMember | Content Creation02/2021 – Present

• Produce visually appealing content graphically for instagram feeds

PROJECTS

HMC Learn

- Is a collaboration community project about a learning management system.
- Participate in the development of system design, including user flow and flowchart.
- Create UI/UX design of LMS (Learning Management System) display by using Design Thinking concept. **Leverage knowledge:** TeamWork, Github, Figma, Figjam

MovieDb Clone

- Built a Movie Catalog App using Flutter, implementing data parsing, state management with Provider, pagination, and service locator (Get It).
- Enhanced UI with custom widgets, WebView for movie trailers, and Search Delegate. Leverage knowledge: Api, Flutter, State Management.

Mandiri News

- Developed a comprehensive News App using Jetpack Compose Clean Architecture, covering essential components such as splash screen, onboarding, home screen, search, and details screen.
- Implemented advanced Android development techniques including Dagger Hilt for dependency injection, Preferences Datastore, Room Database for local storage, and ViewModel integration
 Leverage knowledge: Dagger Hilt, Preferences Datastore, Room Database, MVVM, Clean Architecture.

Stroko

- Collaborate on a capstone project that integrates Machine Learning, Cloud Computing, and Android
- Implemented a robust Android application that utilized Google Maps API to dynamically display and detect nearby hospitals within a 5 km radius from any direction.
- Leverage knowledge: Api, MVVM, Google Maps API, Location-Based Service, Gps markers.

HONORS AND AWARDS

Web Application National Competition of the Proxocoris 2024

Team Leader

- Design innovative application concepts and ideas that are relevant to the competition theme.
- Mentoring the team on a weekly basis using the Notion platform to ensure project progress is on track.
- Create UI/UX design, flowchart, and API configuration for login and register using TypeScript.

Funding Achievers Program Kreativitas Mahasiswa (PKM) skema PKM-RE

Team Member

Manage and produce research content for Instagram and YouTube and Create a personal website

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Technical Skills: Kotlin, Android, Dart, Flutter, Hmtl, Css, JavaScript, API, SQlite, Mysql, Firebase, UI/UX.
- **Tools:** Git, Bash, Notion/Trello, canva.